Guide to the African American Museum & Library at Oakland Audiovisual Collection
African American Museum & Library at Oakland
- Assorted, 1971-2005; 11 videotapes
  Arranged alphabetically by name, organization, title or description.
  - Allen, Bob, discusses his autobiography and working in Hollywood, circa 1980s; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box-folder 1)
  - Benton, Glenn, "The day in a life of a blind man," CNTV California State University East Bay Television, circa 2003; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box-folder 8)
  - Buffalo Soldiers reunion and parade, circa 1992; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box-folder 6)
  - Hamilton County Democratic Party meeting, Tivoli Theatre, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1971-09-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box-folder 2)
  - Merritt Bakery, curfew ride along, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box-folder 3)
  - Minister Farrakhan speaks-- "The Donahue show", 1990-02-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box-folder 4)
  - Retreat, 2005-01; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box-folder 3)
  - Satin, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box-folder 3)
  - Scenes from Fort Bragg, North Carolina, filmed in 1941 by Captain Jabus W. Rawls of the 77th CA (AA), undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box-folder 4)
  - “Send us a lady physician,” Karen Hirst plays Elizabeth Blackwell, Oakland Museum of California Women’s Board, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box-folder 4)
  - 21 parts of light, 1993-11-29; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box-folder 3)
  - Unknown speaker providing translations of English phrases to Wolof and French, labeled 'West Africa tour', 1991; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box-folder 3)
  - Unlabeled, undated; 4 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box-folder 3)
  - Virginia Baker's case, undated; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box-folder 6)